This regular meeting of the Miami Special Utility Authority for today's date,
item number two on the agenda is invocation by the pastor of Activate Church, David Jackson.
David, thanks for being here.
Let's have a word of prayer.
Jesus, just thank you for the gift of life, Lord.
Thank you for our community.
Thank you for these men and women who offer their time and their service to guide us and lead us, Lord.
I just pray that you give them wisdom, give them cooperation and harmony with each other.
Let our community be in unity together.
And let us move forward down the road of progress and building a strong community, Father.
We ask these things in the name of Jesus Christ.
Amen.
Please join me in the pledge.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America
and to the republic for which it stands,
one nation,
under God,
indivisible,
with liberty and justice for all.
Thank you.
Thank you, David.
Item number four is public input and unscheduled personal appearances.
Anyone that wishes to address the authority on any of the agenda items?
There being none, item five is claims.
I'm looking for a consent item.
No consent.
No consent on this one.
Item five is claims.
Do we have a motion to approve the claims as presented?
Motion to approve, Mayor.
And a second?
Second.
Roll call.
Johnson?
Aye.
Weston?
Schultz?
Aye.
Item six is new business.
Dean, any new business?
None, Your Honor.
Seven, staff reports are in your packet.
Eight is community announcements.
Any announcements?
No.
Nine is motion to adjourn.
Motion to adjourn.
And a second, please?
Second.
Weston?
Aye.
Johnson?
Schultz?
Aye.
We're going to move now right into the agenda item.
We're going to move now right into ...